Architecture Slide Collection
Yale University Arts Library
- 20th Century Architecture (Box 41)
  - United States (Box 61)
    - Miscellaneous Cities [Slide box 377] (Box 63)
      - Maryville, TN [Slide box 421] (Box 71)
      - Mashpee Commons, M A (Box 71)
      - Mason City, IA (Box 71)
      - McCook, NE (Box 71)
      - Medford, MA (Box 71)
      - Memphis, TN (Box 71)
      - Merion, PA (Box 71)
      - Methuen, MA (Box 71)
      - Miami, FL (Box 71)
      - Miami Beach, FL (Box 71)
      - Middlebury, CT (Box 71)
      - Middleton, WI (Box 71)
      - Middletown, CT [Slide box 422] (Box 71)
        - Various (Box 71)
        - Houses (Box 71)
          - Various (Box 71)
          - Maplewood (Box 71)
      - Middletown, RI (Box 71)
      - Midland, MI (Box 71)
      - Milbach, PA (Box 71)
      - Milford, CT (Box 71)
      - Millington, CT (Box 71)
      - Milwaukee, WI (Box 71)
      - Minneapolis, MN (Box 71)
        - Various (Box 71)
        - Churches (Box 71)
        - Houses (Box 71)
        - Warehouses (Box 71)
      - Mississippi, State of [Slide box 423] (Box 71)
      - Mockton, VT (Box 71)
      - Monroe, WI (Box 71)
      - Montauk, NY (Box 71)
        - Houses (Box 71)
          - Various (Box 71)
          - Beebe House (Box 71)
          - Danziger Pool House (Box 71)
          - Wiseman House (Box 71)
      - Montecito, CA (Box 71)
        - Various (Box 71)
        - Tremaine House [Slide boxes 423-424] (Box 71)
      - Monterey, CA [Slide box 424] (Box 71)
      - Montpelier, VA (Box 71)
      - Montpelier, VT (Box 71)
      - Mount Desert, ME (Box 71)
        - Various (Box 71)
        - Mount Vernon (Box 71)
          Xx under Virginia
      - Mystic, CT (Box 71)
      - Nantucket Island, MA (Box 71)
        - Various (Box 71)
        - Trubeck & Wislocki Houses (Box 71)
      - Napa Valley, CA (Box 71)
      - Narragansett Pier, RI (Box 71)
      - Nashua, NH (Box 71)
      - Nashville, TN [Slide boxes 424-425] (Box 71)
      - Natchez, MO [Slide box 425] (Box 71)
        - Various (Box 71)
        - D'Evereux (Box 71)
        - Dunleith (Box 71)
        - Gloucester (Box 71)
        - Monteigne (Box 71)
      - Natick, MA (Box 71)
      - Naugatuck, CT (Box 71)
      - Navesick Park, NJ (Box 71)
      - Newark, NJ (Box 71)
      - Newark, OH (Box 71)
      - New Babylon, KS (Box 71)
      - New Bedford, MA (Box 71)
      - New Bern, NC (Box 71)
      - New Canaan, CT (Box 71)
        - Various (Box 71)
        - Boissonnas Houses [Slide box 426] (Box 71)
        - Goode House (Box 71)
        - Goode House (Box 71)
        - Johanssen House (Box 71)
        - Johnson (Glass) House (Box 71)
        - John Rayward House (Box 71)
        - Wiley House (Box 71)
      - New Castle, DE (Box 71)
        - Various (Box 71)
        - George Reed II House [Slide box 427] (Box 72)
      - New Harmony, IN (Box 72)
      - New Haven, CT (Box 72)
        - General (Box 72)
          - Various (Box 72)
          - Views (Box 72)
          - The Green (Box 72)
          - Streets [Slide boxes 427-428] (Box 72)
          - Plans & Maps [Slide box 428] (Box 72)
        - 17th Century (Box 72)
        - 18th Century (Box 72)
        - 19th Century (Box 72)
        - 20th Century (Box 72)
          - Planning (Box 72)
            - Center of City, Project 1941 (Box 72)
            - Church ST. Redevelopment (Box 72)
            - City Government Center, 1966 (Box 72)
            - Civic Improvement Commission, 1910 (Box 72)
            - Oak ST. Redevelopment [Slide boxes 428-429] (Box 72)
            - Yale Graduate School Planning Study [Slide box 429] (Box 72)
          - Banks (Box 72)
          - Cemeteries (Box 72)
          - Churches (Box 72)
            - Various (Box 72)
            - Center Church (Box 72)
            - Christ Church and Parish House (Box 72)
            - Church of the Redeemer (Box 72)
            - United or North Church (Box 72)
            - United Church Parish House (Box 72)
          - Coliseum (Box 72)
          - Garages [Slide boxes 429-430] (Box 72)
          - Government Buildings [Slide box 430] (Box 72)
            - Various (Box 72)
            - City Hall (Box 72)
            - Central Firehouse (Box 72)
            - Goffe ST. Firehouse (Box 72)
          - Hospitals (Box 72)
            - Various (Box 72)
            - Psychiatric Institute [Slide boxes 430-431] (Box 72)
          - Hotels [Slide box 431] (Box 72)
          - Houses (Box 72)
            - Various (Box 72)
            - Anderson House (Box 72)
            - Atwater House (Box 72)
            - Beers Street House (Box 72)
            - Berrian House (Box 72)
            - Bishop House (Box 72)
            - Willis Bristol House (Box 72)
            - Dana House [Slide box 432] (Box 72)
            - Davies-Wallace House (Box 72)
            - Dwight House (Box 72)
            - Farnam House (Box 72)
            - Hillhouse House (Box 72)
            - Ingersoll House (Box 72)
            - Maple Cottage (Box 72)
            - Norton House (Box 72)
            - Perit House (Box 72)
            - John Pierpont House (Box 72)
            - Porter House (Box 72)
            - Ithiel Town House (Box 72)
            - Trowbridge House (Box 72)
          - Housing (Box 72)
          - Industrial Buildings (Box 72)
          - Libraries [Slide box 433] (Box 73)
          - Office Buildings (Box 73)
          - Monuments (Box 73)
          - Schools (Box 73)
            - Yale (Box 73)
              - General (Box 73)
                - Various (Box 73)
                - Maps/Plans (Box 73)
                - Early Prints, paintings (Box 73)
                - Air Views [Slide boxes 433-434] (Box 73)
                - Schematic plan, How Yale grew [Slide box 434] (Box 73)
                - John Trumbull, plan (Box 73)
                - John Russell Pope, plans proposals (Box 73)
                - J.G. Rogers, drawings (Box 73)
                - Students Rooms (Box 73)
              - Accelerator Lab (Box 73)
              - Alumni War Memorial [Slide box 435] (Box 73)
              - Anlyan Center (Box 73)
              - Art & Architecture Building (Box 73)
                - Plans & Sections (Box 73)
                - Exterior (Box 73)
                - Interior (Box 73)
              - Art Gallery I-III [Slide box 436] (Box 73)
              - Art Gallery IV: 1952-1953 (Box 73)
                - Various (Box 73)
                - Exterior (Box 73)
                - Interior (Box 73)
                - Various (Box 73)
                - 1st Floor (Box 73)
                - 2nd Floor [Slide box 437] (Box 73)
                - 3rd Floor (Box 73)
                - Staircase (Box 73)
                - Exhibitions (Box 73)
                - Various (Box 73)
                - American Art from Alumni (Box 73)
              - Athletic Group, Yale Bowl (Box 73)
              - Battell Chapel (Box 73)
              - Becton Science Center (Box 73)
              - Boyer Center Molecular Medicine (Box 73)
              - British Art Center (Box 73)
                - Various [Slide boxes 437-438] (Box 73)
                - Exterior [Slide box 438] (Box 73)
                - Interior (Box 73)
              - Byers Hall (Box 73)
              - Computer Lab (Box 73)
              - Connecticut Hall [Slide box 439] (Box 74)
              - Divinity School (Box 74)
              - Durfee Hall (Box 74)
              - Dwight Hall II, 1886 (Box 74)
              - Farnam Hall (Box 74)
              - First College House (Box 74)
              - Fraternity Houses (Box 74)
              - Gibbs Lab (Box 74)
              - Graduate Housing (Box 74)
              - Greeley Memorial (Box 74)
              - Hall of Graduate Studies (Box 74)
              - Harness Tower [Slide boxes 439-440] (Box 74)
              - Ingalls Rink [Slide box 440] (Box 74)
              - Kline Biology Tower (Box 74)
              - Kline Geology Lab (Box 74)
              - Lawrence Hall (Box 74)
              - Leet Oliver (Box 74)
              - Libraries (Box 74)
                - Various (Box 74)
                - I: Dwight Chapel (Box 74)
                - II: Sterling Memorial (Box 74)
                - Various (Box 74)
                - Exterior (Box 74)
                - Interior [Slide box 441] (Box 74)
              - Beinecke Rare Book (Box 74)
              - Cross Campus Library (Box 74)
                - Various (Box 74)
              - Linsley-Chittenden (Box 74)
              - Math Building (Box 74)
              - Medical School (Box 74)
              - Morse College (Box 74)
              - Noah Porter Gate (Box 74)
              - North Sheffield (Box 74)
              - Old Campus (Box 74)
              - Osborn Hall (Box 74)
              - Payne White Gym (Box 74)
              - Pea body Museum (Box 74)
              - Phelps Hall & Gateway (Box 74)
              - 77 Prospect Street [Slide boxes 442] (Box 74)
              - Residence Colleges (Box 74)
              - Secret Societies (Box 74)
                Xx Arch. U.S., New Haven, Yale U. Fraternity Houses & Tombs
              - Sheffield (Box 74)
              - Slifka Center for Jewish Life (Box 74)
              - Sterling Hall of Medicine (Box 74)
              - Sterling Law Buildings (Box 74)
              - Stiles & Morse Colleges (Box 74)
              - Stoeckel Hall (Box 74)
              - Street Hall [Slide boxes 442-443] (Box 74)
              - Theater [Slide box 443] (Box 74)
              - Winchester Hall (Box 74)
              - Woodbridge Hall (Box 74)
              - Woolsey Hall (Box 74)
              - Stations (Box 74)
      - New Hope, PA (Box 74)
      - New Jersey (Box 74)
      - New Kensington, PA (Box 74)
      - New London, CT (Box 74)
        - Various (Box 74)
        - Frederic Newcomb House [Slide boxes 443-444] (Box 74)
      - New Orleans, LA [Slide box 444] (Box 74)
        - Various (Box 74)
        - Plans and Views (Box 74)
        - Houses (Box 74)
        - Squares (Box 74)
      - New Paltz, NY (Box 74)
      - Newport, RI (Box 74)
        - Various (Box 74)
          - Brick Market (Box 74)
        - Cemeteries (Box 74)
        - Churches (Box 74)
          - Touri Synagogue (Box 74)
          - Trinity Church [Slide box 445] (Box 75)
        - Government Buildings (Box 75)
        - Houses (Box 75)
          - Various (Box 75)
          - Isaac Bell House (Box 75)
          - Breakers (Box 75)
          - Chateau-Sur-Mer (Box 75)
          - Robert Goelet House (Box 75)
          - Griswold House (Box 75)
          - Hunter House [Slide box 446] (Box 75)
          - King House (Box 75)
          - Kingscote (Box 75)
          - Malbone (Hall) House (Box 75)
          - Marble House (Box 75)
          - Morgan House (Box 75)
          - Ochre Court (Box 75)
          - Rosecliff (Box 75)
          - H.S.C. Taylor House (Box 75)
          - Watts-Sherman House (Box 75)
        - Libraries [Slide boxes 446-447] (Box 75)
        - Recreation [Slide box 447] (Box 75)
      - Newport Beach, CA (Box 75)
      - Newport News, VA (Box 75)
      - Newton, MA (Box 75)
      - New York, NY (Box 75)
        - Various (Box 75)
        - Plans/Planning (Box 75)
        - Views (Box 75)
        - Streets (Box 75)
        - Airports (Box 75)
          - Idlewild (Kennedy Airport) (Box 75)
        - American Airlines Terminal (Box 75)
        - First National City Bank (Box 75)
        - Gulf Services Station [Slide box 448] (Box 75)
        - Pan American Terminal (Box 75)
        - TWA Terminal (Box 75)
        - Armories (Box 75)
        - Banks (Box 75)
        - Bridges (Box 75)
        - Churches (Box 75)
          - Various (Box 75)
          - Grace Church (Box 75)
          - ST. Patrick's Cathedral (Box 75)
          - St. Paul's Chapel (Box 75)
          - St. Peter's at Citicorp (Box 75)
          - Trinity Church [Slide box 449] (Box 75)
        - Clubs (Box 75)
        - Expositions (Box 75)
          - World's Fair 1939 (Box 75)
            - Various [Slide boxes 449-450] (Box 75)
            - Murals [Slide box 450] (Box 75)
            - Sculpture (Box 75)
          - World's Fair, 1964-1965 (Box 75)
        - Government Buildings (Box 75)
          - Various (Box 75)
          - City Hall (Box 75)
          - Islamic Cultural Center (Box 75)
          - United Nations Building [Slide boxes 450-451] (Box 75)
        - Hospitals [Slide box 451] (Box 76)
        - Hotels (Box 76)
        - Houses (Box 76)
          - Various (Box 76)
          - Harkness House (Box 76)
        - Houses – Apartments (Box 76)
        - Housing (Box 76)
        - Industrial Buildings (Box 76)
        - Libraries (Box 76)
        - Markets (Box 76)
          - Various (Box 76)
          - South Street [Slide box 452] (Box 76)
        - Monuments (Box 76)
        - Museums (Box 76)
          - Various (Box 76)
          - Guggenheim (Box 76)
          - Metropolitan Museum of Art (Box 76)
          - Museum of Modern Art (Box 76)
          - Whitney Museum [Slide box 453] (Box 76)
        - Office Buildings (Box 76)
          - Various (Box 76)
          - A.T&T Corporation Headquaters (Box 76)
          - Asia House (Box 76)
          - Barclay-Vesey (Telephone) (Box 76)
          - Battery Park City (Box 76)
          - Bayard Building (Box 76)
          - Chrysler Building (Box 76)
          - Citicorp (Box 76)
          - DeVinne [Slide box 454] (Box 76)
          - Empire State Building (Box 76)
          - Flatiron (Fuller) Building (Box 76)
          - Ford Foundation Building (Box 76)
          - Guernsey (Box 76)
          - Haughwout (Box 76)
          - Hines (Box 76)
          - Hutton (Box 76)
          - Lever House (Box 76)
          - McGraw-Hill Building (Box 76)
          - Newspaper Row (Box 76)
          - Pan Am Building (Box 76)
          - Pepsi Cola Building (Box 76)
          - Rockefeller Center (Box 76)
          - Seagram Building (Box 76)
          - Singer (Box 76)
          - Woolworth Building (Box 76)
          - World Trade Center [Slide box 455] (Box 76)
          - New World Trade Center (Box 76)
        - Parks (Box 76)
          - Various (Box 76)
          - Central Park (Box 76)
            - Various (Box 76)
            - Central Park Perimeter (Box 76)
        - Prisons (Box 76)
        - Schools [Slide box 455-456] (Box 76)
        - Squares [Slide box 456] (Box 76)
        - Stations (Box 76)
          - Various (Box 76)
          - PENN Station (Box 76)
          - Grand Central Station (Box 76)
        - Stores (Box 76)
        - Streets (Box 76)
        - Theaters [Slide boxes 456-457] (Box 76)
      - Niagara Falls, NY [Slide box 457] (Box 77)
      - Norfolk, VA (Box 77)
        - Various (Box 77)
        - Adam Through-good House (Box 77)
      - Norman, OK (Box 77)
      - North Dartmouth, MA (Box 77)
      - North Easton, MA (Box 77)
        - Government Buildings (Box 77)
        - Houses [Slide box 458] (Box 77)
        - Libraries (Box 77)
        - Stations (Box 77)
      - Northampton, MA (Box 77)
      - North Tarrytown, NY (Box 77)
      - Norwalk, CT (Box 77)
        - Legrand Lockwood Mansion (Box 77)
          - Exterior (Box 77)
          - Interior (Box 77)
            - Various (Box 77)
            - Card Room (Box 77)
            - Drawing (Sitting) (Box 77)
            - Entrance Hall (Box 77)
            - Italian Room (Box 77)
            - Library (Box 77)
            - Music Room (Box 77)
      - Norwalk, OH (Box 77)
      - Norwich, CT (Box 77)
      - Oakland, CA [Slide box 459] (Box 77)
      - Oak Park, IL (Box 77)
        - Various (Box 77)
        - Unity Temple (Box 77)
        - Houses (Box 77)
          - Various (Box 77)
          - Moore House (Box 77)
          - Wright House (Box 77)
      - Oak Ridge, TN (Box 77)
      - Oberlin, OH (Box 77)
      - Ocean Grove, NJ (Box 77)
      - Ocean Springs, MO (Box 77)
      - Odessa, DE (Box 77)
      - Ojai, CA [Slide box 460] (Box 77)
      - Okemos, MI (Box 77)
      - Oklahoma City, OK (Box 77)
      - Old Laguna Pueblo, NM (Box 77)
      - Old Lyme, CT (Box 77)
      - Old Salem, NC (Box 77)
      - Old Westbury, Long Island, NY (Box 77)
      - Olympia, WA (Box 77)
      - Omaha, NE (Box 77)
      - Orange, CT (Box 77)
      - Orinda, CA (Box 77)
      - Orlando, FL (Box 77)
      - Orwell, VT (Box 77)
      - Oshkosh, WI (Box 77)
      - Oswego, OR (Box 77)
      - Overbrook, PA [Slide box 461] (Box 77)
      - Owatonna, MI (Box 77)
      - Oyster Bay, Lon Island, NY (Box 77)
      - Pacific Grove, CA (Box 77)
      - Pacific Palisades, CA (Box 77)
        - Various (Box 77)
        - St. Matthew's Parish Church (Box 77)
      - Palm Beach, FL (Box 77)
      - Palm Springs, CA (Box 77)
      - Palo Alto, CA (Box 77)
      - Palo Colorado Canyon, CA [Slide box 462] (Box 77)
      - Palos Verdes, CA (Box 77)
      - Paradise Valle, AZ (Box 77)
      - Pasadena, CA (Box 77)
        - Various (Box 77)
        - R.R. Blacker House (Box 77)
        - Gamble House (Box 77)
          - Exterior (Box 77)
          - Interior (Box 77)
            - Various [Slide boxes 462-463] (Box 77–78)
            - Lillian B. Ladd House [Slide box 463] (Box 78)
      - Pawtucket, RI (Box 78)
      - Peekskill, NY (Box 78)
      - Pennsylvania, State of (Box 78)
        - Bucks County, PA (Box 78)
      - Pensacola, FL (Box 78)
      - Peru, IL (Box 78)
      - Peru, VT (Box 78)
      - Philadelphia, PA (Box 78)
        - General (Box 78)
        - Plans & Planning (Box 78)
          - Various (Box 78)
          - Model, 1949 [Slide boxes 463-464] (Box 78)
        - Banks [Slide box 464] (Box 78)
          - Various (Box 78)
          - First National Bank (Box 78)
          - Philadelphia Savings Foundation Society (Box 78)
          - Provident Trust Company (Box 78)
          - Union Trust Company (Box 78)
        - Bridges (Box 78)
        - Churches [Slide boxes 464-465] (Box 78)
        - Clubs [Slide box 465] (Box 78)
        - Expositions (Box 78)
        - Government Buildings (Box 78)
          - Various (Box 78)
          - City Hall (Box 78)
          - Independence Hall (Box 78)
        - Hospitals (Box 78)
        - Hotels (Box 78)
        - Houses (Box 78)
          - Various [Slide boxes 465-466] (Box 78)
          - Lemon Hill [Slide box 466] (Box 78)
          - Moore House (Box 78)
          - Mount Pleasant (Box 78)
          - Neil-Mauran House (Box 78)
          - 238 St. - 3rd St. (Box 78)
          - Strawberry (Box 78)
          - Woodford (Box 78)
        - Housing (Box 78)
          - Various (Box 78)
          - Guild House (Box 78)
          - Mill Creek (Box 78)
        - Libraries (Box 78)
        - Museums (Box 78)
          - Various (Box 78)
          - Penn. Academy (Box 78)
        - Offices [Slide boxes 467-468] (Box 78)
        - Prisons [Slide box 468] (Box 78)
        - Schools (Box 78)
          - Various (Box 78)
          - University of Penn (Box 78)
            - Various (Box 78)
            - Biology Building (Box 78)
            - Dorms (Box 78)
            - Library (Box 78)
            - Richards Medical [Slide boxes 468-469] (Box 78)
        - Stations [Slide box 469] (Box 79)
        - Stores (Box 79)
        - Theaters (Box 79)
      - Phoenix, AZ (Box 79)
        - Various (Box 79)
        - Houses (Box 79)
          - Various (Box 79)
          - Taliesin West (Box 79)
            - Exterior (Box 79)
            - Interior [Slide box 470] (Box 79)
      - Phoenixville, PA (Box 79)
      - Piercefield, NY (Box 79)
      - Pittsburgh, PA (Box 79)
        - Various (Box 79)
        - Government Buildings (Box 79)
          - Various (Box 79)
          - Allegheny County Court House (Box 79)
        - Houses (Box 79)
        - Libraries [Slide box 471] (Box 79)
        - Office Buildings (Box 79)
      - Plainfield, IN (Box 79)
      - Plano, IL (Box 79)
      - Pleasantville, NY (Box 79)
      - Plimouth Plantation (Box 79)
      - Plymouth, MI (Box 79)
      - Pomfret, CT (Box 79)
      - Port Chester, NY (Box 79)
      - Portland, ME (Box 79)
      - Portland, OR (Box 79)
        - Various (Box 79)
        - Churches [Slide box 472] (Box 79)
        - Government Buildings (Box 79)
        - Houses (Box 79)
      - Portsmouth, NH (Box 79)
        - Various (Box 79)
        - Governor Langdon House (Box 79)
        - Moffatt-Ladd House (Box 79)
        - Rundley-May House (Box 79)
        - John Wentworth House (Winterthur & MMA) (Box 79)
        - Wentworth-Gardner House (Box 79)
      - Portsmouth, RI (Box 79)
      - Pottersville, NJ (Box 79)
      - Pottstown, PA (Box 79)
      - Poughkeepsie, NY (Box 79)
      - Princeton, NJ (Box 79)
        - Various (Box 79)
        - Houses [Slide box 473] (Box 79)
          - Benacerraf House (Box 79)
          - Claghorne House (Box 79)
          - Claghorne House (Box 79)
          - Shulman House (Box 79)
        - Schools (Box 79)
          - Various (Box 79)
          - Gordon Wu Hall (Box 79)
      - Proctorsville, VT (Box 79)
      - Prospect Park, PA (Box 79)
      - Providence, RI (Box 79)
        - Various (Box 79)
        - Churches (Box 79)
        - Houses [Slide box 474] (Box 79)
      - Provincetown, MA (Box 79)
      - Pullman, IL (Box 79)
      - Purchase, NY (Box 79)
      - Quincy, MA (Box 79)
      - Racine, WI (Box 79)
        - Various (Box 79)
        - Houses (Box 79)
          - Various (Box 79)
          - Hardy House (Box 79)
          - Johnson House (Box 79)
        - Industrial Buildings (Box 79)
          - Johnson Wax Building (Box 79)
            - Various (Box 79)
            - Exterior (Box 79)
            - Interior [Slide box 475] (Box 80)
            - Research Towers (Box 80)
      - Radburn, NJ (Box 80)
      - Raleigh, NC (Box 80)
      - Ranchos de Taos, NM (Box 80)
      - Rensselaer, NY (Box 80)
      - Reston, VA (Box 80)
      - Rhinebeck, NY (Box 80)
      - Richfield Springs, NY (Box 80)
      - Richland Center, WI (Box 80)
      - Richmond, CA (Box 80)
      - Richmond, VA (Box 80)
        - Various (Box 80)
        - Churches (Box 80)
        - Government Buildings [Slide boxes 476] (Box 80)
        - Houses (Box 80)
      - River Edge, NY (Box 80)
      - River Forest, IL (Box 80)
      - Riverside, IL (Box 80)
        - Various (Box 80)
        - Avery Coonley House (Box 80)
      - Riviera Beach, FL (Box 80)
      - Rochester, NY (Box 80)
      - Rockingham, VT [Slide box 477] (Box 80)
      - Rockport, ME (Box 80)
      - Sacramento, CA (Box 80)
      - Sagaponack, NY (Box 80)
      - St. Augustine, FL (Box 80)
      - St. Genevieve, MO (Box 80)
      - St. Louis, MO (Box 80)
        - Various (Box 80)
        - Pruitt-Igoe Housing (Box 80)
        - Airport Terminal Building (Box 80)
        - Wainwright Building [Slide boxes 477-478] (Box 80)
        - Wainwright Tomb [Slide box 478] (Box 80)
        - World's Fair, 1904 (Box 80)
      - St. Mary's City, MD (Box 80)
      - St. Paul, MN (Box 80)
      - Salem, MA (Box 80)
        - Various (Box 80)
        - Houses (Box 80)
          - Various (Box 80)
          - Pierce Nichols House (Box 80)
          - Pingree House (Box 80)
      - Salem, OR (Box 80)
      - Salt Lake City, UT [Slide boxes 478-479] (Box 80)
      - San Antonio, TX [Slide box 479] (Box 80)
      - San Carlo, CA (Box 80)
      - San Diego, CA (Box 80)
        - Various (Box 80)
        - Salk Institute (Box 80)
      - Sandusky, OH (Box 80)
      - Sandwich, MA (Box 80)
        - Captain's House (Box 80)
        - Quail Hollow (Box 80)
        - Salt Box House (Box 80)
      - San Fernando, CA (Box 80)
      - San Francisco, CA [Slide box 480] (Box 80)
        - Various (Box 80)
        - Plans/Planning (Box 80)
        - Views (Box 80)
        - Churches (Box 80)
        - Expositions (Box 80)
        - Government Buildings (Box 80)
        - Hospitals (Box 80)